Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Computer Science, Stanford Computer Forum Distinguished Lecture Series, Videorecordings V0058
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Videorecordings, 1981-1998; Accession ARCH-2017-023
  - unlabeled, 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting World Symposium Japan, 2001 May - Jun; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting, World Japan Symposium, WSJ-Binder, 2001; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 3)
  - Visiting scholar certificate Suzanne Bill's BBQ events, 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - The Bornstein Burn forum video, 2000 Dec 15; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Edward McKwavy retirement Stanford Computer Forum Juliam Clark, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Archiving Digital Libraries, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Forum Video test, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - unlabeled, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Forum Video test, 2000 Dec 7; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Good forum video, 2000 Dec 7; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Compressed trailers, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Final Project Files back-up log to date, 2000 Sep 1; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Trailers pointer and compressed files, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Roberts, Mobile, Library, Robotics, Winograd, Security, Levoy trailers, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Full Sequences (Quicktime) Robotics, Library, Mobile, Winograd, Roberts, Security, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Mark Levoy full Quicktime Sequence, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts - interview Teaching at Harvard, HS, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Trailers (Quicktime) Roberts, Mobile, Library, Robotics, Winograd, Security, Levoy, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts interview future Tech Worries, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts - Interview student breakdown, chart, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts - Interview Childhood aptitude test, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts- Interview Student at Harvard, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Eric Roberts - Interview thrill of Technology, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS Ken Shows Kinematic Arm, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS Luis Shows Romeo, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS Diego Demos Haptics 5, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS 1. Diego Shows Hoptics -2, 2. Diego Shows Hoptics, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/GS Luis, Ken Demo Romeo, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS Ken Intros Haptics, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS Audience Shot 1, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/ GS 1. How to Make a Robot, 2. Salisbury Pointer file- yet another backup!, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - 1. Mobile Comp. 2. Robotics, 3. Winograd Final Sequences (rough CD), 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury / GS 1. Luis Shows Romeo 2. Ken at Whiteboard, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury /GS Pulley Group + Salisbury Pointer Backup, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/GS Diego Shows Haptics, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/GS Diego Demos Haptics 4, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/GS Luis Shows Romeo 3, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Project Salisbury/GS 1. Girl doing Haptics, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Ken Salisbury / GS 1. Ken at Whiteboard 2. Ken explains grad school, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)
  - Salisbury/GS 1. Ken Welcomes GS 2. Romeo, Robotics lab 3. Diego shows Haptics 3 demos + Salisbury pointer file backup, 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 3)